firemansamonline.com 2008-12-28

# HiT Entertainment Limited - Privacy Policy

| 

| HIT Entertainment Privacy Policy  
---  
Statement of Intent and Our Commitment to Privacy | Parents  
Agreement to this Privacy Policy | When PII and Non-PII May Be Requested   
Use of PII  | Opting Out   
E-Commerce  | Safety and Security  
Use of Technology | Third Party Advertisements  
International User Notice  | Reviewing, Updating and Deleting Personal information   
Comments, Questions or Suggestions  | Children's Privacy  
  
THIS PRIVACY POLICY WAS LAST UPDATED ON 24 JULY 2008. 

Welcome to HIT Entertainment Limited's family of web sites ("Web Sites") and thank you for visiting. We are committed to providing a quality experience and have developed our Web Sites to provide an informative and entertaining experience for users. This Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") explains HIT Entertainment Limited's online information practices and describes how HIT Entertainment Limited collects, uses and shares any of the following information obtained from and about our online visitors (i) personally identifiable information ("PII") such as, your first and last name, address, telephone number, screen name, email address or credit card information and (ii) other information which does not allow us to personally identify you ("Non-PII") such as, your first name, post code, city, age, gender, product and promotional preferences and household characteristics like presence of children or income bracket information. Our newsletters and data collection are generally aimed at parents and are covered by this policy. We have separate information practices and policies covering collection of children's information here.   
  
**Parents**  
We encourage parents/guardians to become involved in their children's online experience. Please discuss use of the Internet and disclosure of information on our Web Sites or any web site with your children. Additionally, parents please discuss this Privacy Policy with your children so they better understand how to use our Web Sites and the kinds of information we may ask of them.   

Back to top  
  
**AGREEMENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND PRIVACY POLICY MODIFICATIONS**   
By using our Web Sites, you are agreeing to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, or any of its terms, please do not use this Web Site or any other HIT Entertainment Limited Web Site. From time to time, and at any time, this Privacy Policy may be revised or changed. We will notify you of a material change by placing a notice on our Web Sites or by sending a notice to the primary email address you have specified. All users of our Web Sites should review this Privacy Policy periodically to be up to date on our most current privacy policies and practices. 

This Privacy Policy only applies to information HIT Entertainment Limited collects online and not information collected offline. Additionally, this Privacy Policy only applies to HIT Entertainment Limited's Web Sites and not to third party web sites to which we link. 

Back to top  
  
**WHEN PII AND NON-PII MAY BE REQUESTED**   
Registration or input of PII may be requested for participation in activities such as sweepstakes, contests, marketing and promotional activities, surveys, e-mail newsletters, e-commerce or sending questions/comments to us. 

The types of PII we may request include parent's name and/child's name, e-mail address, mailing address and/or birth date. 

Back to top  
  
**USE OF PII**   
We may use PII collected at the site for the following purposes: (i) to personalize and enhance our Web Sites and your Internet experience, (ii) to provide you with additional product and service opportunities; (iii) for internal marketing and demographic studies, and (iv) to contact you for non-marketing purposes (such as for feedback or customer service). 

The PII you disclose may be shared with third parties that provide support of our Web Sites' activities, such as those who may administer an activity for us, those conducting online contests and sweepstakes and shipping companies or fulfillment houses that may deliver a product, prize or premium. These third parties will use your PII to perform their functions and may not use it for other purposes. 

In addition, we may disclose PII in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request; where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use; to protect the rights, property or safety of our Web Sites, users of our Web Sites and others; or as otherwise required by law or consistent with legal requirements. 

In the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization or other similar event, your PII may be transferred or shared with our successors or assigns. 

We may also share PII collected from one of our Web Sites with any other of our Web Sites and with other HIT Entertainment companies. 

HIT Entertainment Limited may, from time to time, share adults' information with unrelated third parties (e.g., other kids content providers) to provide them with additional product or service opportunities. See the "Opting-Out" section below regarding your choices with respect to future communications. 

Back to top  
  
**OPTING-OUT**   
To receive e-mails about HIT Entertainment Limited, including special offers, products and other information you might find interesting, you may express your preferences regarding these communications at the time of registration or at the time of collection of PII. If you are receiving such emails from HIT Entertainment Limited and wish to opt-out of receiving them, you can do so by (i) clicking on the designated unsubscribe link within the e-mail d, (ii) choosing Contact Us from the appropriate section on the Web Site and entering "Remove," along with the applicable email address in the Comments box, or (iii) writing us at: 

US Address:  
HIT Entertainment Limited  
Attn: Online Privacy Administrator  
230 Park Avenue South  
Suite 1300  
New York, NY 10003   
USA   
Tel: 212-463-9623 

As noted above, we may share adults' PII with unrelated third parties to provide them with additional product or service opportunities. If at some point you grant us permission to transfer your information for these purposes and later decide that you no longer want us to do so, simply send us an e-mail at [privacyadmin@hitentertainment.com](mailto:privacyadmin@hitentertainment.com), and we will edit your preferences accordingly. 

Back to top  
  
**E-COMMERCE**   
Purchases through our Web Sites may require disclosure of your PII, your credit card information and information about the name and address of the person receiving the purchases. The credit card information may be subject to verification by the issuing credit card company or other company. Sales and shipping records will also be generated and maintained.   

Back to top  
  
**SAFETY AND SECURITY**   
We have implemented various technical and organizational measures to secure and protect the information provided by you. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. While we try to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us. You use the Web Sites, and provide us with personal information, at your own risk. To the extent reasonably necessary to protect a user's safety, we may collect his or her name, address, and/or email address. To protect our security, to protect us against liability, or as required by law, we may collect a user's name and email address. PII collected pursuant to this provision will not be used for any other purpose.   

Back to top  
  
**USE OF TECHNOLOGY**   
USE OF COOKIES  
During the course of any visit to a HIT Entertainment Limited Web Site, the pages you see, along with something called a "cookie", are downloaded to your computer. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. HIT Entertainment Limited cookies do not contain any PII, but they do enable us to provide features such as personalization. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser. For additional information on finding and controlling your cookies, please see the provisions at the end of this Privacy Policy entitled "HOW TO FIND AND CONTROL YOUR COOKIES." 

Cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used. Users have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued or to block all cookies. If you set the browser to block cookies, it will result in certain personalized services not being provided to the users on that computer. 

WEB BEACONS  
Our Web Sites contain electronic images (called a "single-pixel gif" or "Web beacon") that allow us to count page views or to access cookies. In general, any electronic image viewed as part of a web site, including an ad banner, can act as a web beacon. Web beacons are typically very small, 1 by 1 pixel size, banner like files, but their presence can be easily seen within Internet Explorer by clicking on "View" and then on "Source." Our Web beacons do not collect, gather, monitor or share any personal information about visitors to our Web Sites, they are just the technique we use to compile our anonymous, aggregated statistics about web site usage. 

COMPUTER PROFILES   
We also collect and accumulate other anonymous data that helps us understand and analyze the Internet experience of our visitors. For example, we accumulate visitor data relating to referring domains, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. We also record number of visits, paths taken and time spent on Web Sites and pages. None of this information is personally identifiable and we only share this information in the aggregate, reflecting overall web site or Internet usage trends. 

Back to top  
  
**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISEMENTS**   
We may include on our Web Sites banner or text advertisements from third parties, or for web sites operated by third parties, that are not sponsors of and are not affiliated with our Web Sites. As such, we are not responsible for the content, polices or practices of the web sites operated by these third parties. In addition, these advertisements and/or links do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement or approval by us of the content, policies or practices of these web sites. All users should check the relevant web site's privacy policy and terms of use in order to understand their policies and practices regarding the collection and use of PII. For more information on third party ad servers generally, please see [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).   

Back to top  
  
**INTERNATIONAL USER NOTICE**   
As HIT Entertainment Limited operates globally, it may be necessary to transfer your information internationally, and in particular, your information may be transferred to and processed in the United States or the United Kingdom. For residents of the European Union: the data protection and other laws of other countries outside of the European Union may not be as comprehensive as those of the European Union; please be assured that we take steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using this site, you agree to have your information used and transferred to the United States as set forth in this policy.   

Back to top  
  
**REVIEWING, UPDATING AND DELETING PERSONAL INFORMATION**   
Users may review their PII at any time. If you would like to review, modify or delete this information, please use the Contact Us form on a Web Site and enter your detailed request in the text box, or write us with your detailed request at: 

**US Address:**  
HIT Entertainment Limited  
Attn: Online Privacy Administrator  
230 Park Avenue South  
Suite 1300  
New York, NY 10003   
USA   
Tel: 212-463-9623 

Back to top  
  
**COMMENTS, QUESTIONS OR SUGGESTIONS**   
If you would like to communicate with us about our Privacy Policy, please use the Contact Us form on a Web Site and enter your comments in the text box, or write us at: 

****US Address:****  
HIT Entertainment Limited  
Attn: Online Privacy Administrator  
230 Park Avenue South  
Suite 1300  
New York, NY 10003   
USA   
Tel: 212-463-9623 

Back to top  
  
**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**   
Children can surf our Web Sites, view content, and download materials without HIT Entertainment Limited collecting PII. To enable their participation in certain of the interactive features at our site, we may ask children to provide us with PII. For example, we may collect an e-mail address from a child for the sole purpose of responding directly to a specific online request (e.g., to send electronic postcards; to participate in a contest, sweepstakes, or competition; or to ask a question or send a comment). We also may collect a child's and a parent's online contact information in order to send the child periodic communications, such as online newsletters, site updates, or password reminders.   

Back to top  
  
|
